<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Movies &amp; TV Show</string>

    <string name="circled">Media that is live streamed can be recorded through certain media players such as VLC player, or through the use of a Screen Recorder.\10\10 There are also new marketing concepts.For example, the Berlin Philharmonic Orchestra sells Internet live streams of whole concerts, instead of several CDs or similar fixed media, by their so-called Digital Concert Hall using YouTube for trailing purposes only.</string>
    <string name="tvfirmad">Designing a network protocol to support streaming media raises many problems.Video coding formats include H.264, HEVC, VP8 or VP9.\10\10Encoded audio and video streams are assembled in a container bitstream such as MP4, FLV, WebM, ASF or ISMA.</string>
    <string name="voot">Voot Kids, Voot Originals, and news from Network 18’s array of news channels,With over 50,000 hours of exciting content across genres, languages and audiences, Voot is made for those with varying choices and preferences. Voot offers the biggest TV shows from Colors Hindi, MTV, Colors Infinity, Colors Telugu, Colors Tamil, Colors Kannada, Colors Marathi, Colors Bangla, Colors Gujarati, Nickelodeon and Comedy Central.</string>
    <string name="vpn_process_name">:DefendService</string>
    <string name="zeetv">At ZEE5, we believe that for entertainment to come alive, you need to feel it! With 12 Navigational and Featured languages across TV Shows, Movies, Original Web Series, International Shows, Acclaimed Plays and much more. Enjoy unlimited entertainment with 80+ LIVE TV channels and 100,000+ hours of video content in the language of your comfort for an experience that feels like home.</string>

    <string name="reporterd">The audio stream is compressed to make the file size smaller using an audio coding format such as MP3, Vorbis, AAC or Opus.\10\10The video stream is compressed using a video coding format to make the file size smaller.Datagram protocols, such as the User Datagram Protocol (UDP), send the media stream as a series of small packets.This is simple and efficient; however, there is no mechanism within the protocol to guarantee delivery. It is up to the receiving application to detect loss or corruption and recover data using error correction techniques. If data is lost, the stream may suffer a dropout</string>
    <string name="racerd">A broadband speed of 2 Mbit/s or more is recommended for streaming standard definition video without experiencing buffering or skips, especially live video, for example to a Roku, Apple TV, Google TV or a Sony TV Blu-ray Disc Player.</string>
    <string name="escannerd">Useful – and typical – applications of the streaming concept are, for example, long video lectures performed online on the Internet.An advantage of this presentation is that these lectures can be very long, indeed, although they can always be interrupted or repeated at arbitrary places.Livestreaming platforms such as Twitch may also incorporate a video on demand system that allows automatic recording of live broadcasts so that they can be watched later.</string>
    <string name="hotstar">Hotstar is India’s largest premium streaming platform with more than 100,000 hours of drama and movies in 17 languages, and coverage of every major global sporting event.Launched in 2015, it is one of India’s most downloaded apps and has attracted more than 350 million downloads on the back of a highly evolved video streaming technology and high attention to quality of experience across devices.</string>
    <string name="sonylive">SonyLIV is one platform, where 24/7 entertainment is a promise. SonyLIV App brings to its viewers a wide variety of movies, TV shows, live cricket streaming, breaking news and much more.SonyLIV is the single destination for popular content from Sony Entertainment Network Channels:SET MAX,SAB TV,Sony SIX,Sony PIX,AXN,Sony ESPN,Sony MIX,Sony Le PLEX,Republic TV,Sony Marathi,Sony BBC Earth</string>
    <string name="aajtak">Aaj Tak, Indias most watched Hindi TV news channel, available on app for free. Free news app brings to you Live TV, latest news in Hindi (हिंदी समाचार), breaking news, news alerts (ताज़ा हिन्दी खबर), national news, international news (अंतरराष्ट्रीय समाचार), local news, news from states, sports news (खेल समाचार), Bollywood News, news from politics, crime (जुर्म) news and religion news (धर्म). Aaj Tak is India’s most awarded, most-watched and most trusted news source. Download the Aaj Tak app on your Smartphone and watch Aaj Tak news channel Live and Aaj Tak program videos (वीडियो), TV shows from wherever you are, read all the latest news, watch Live TV, News Videos and see the latest pictures.</string>
    <string name="indiatv">The official IndiaTV News App brings you the latest news, breaking news, live updates on trending topics from India, Politics, Business, Entertainment, Bollywood, Sports, Technology and International Events.</string>
    <string name="Abpnews">The official ABP Live News app brings you the latest news app in Hindi news headlines (ताज़ा खबर हिन्दी), in 6 different languages and multiple geographies, breaking news in Hindi from India (इंडिया न्यूज़) and around the world (दुनिया न्यूज़). It features real-time live news from India’s No.1 News Channel – ABP News channel, ABP Ananda(Bengali), ABP Asmita(Gujarati), ABP Majha(Marathi) and ABP Ganga(news from Uttar Pradesh / Uttrakhand)</string>
    <string name="DDNews">The DD News APP is the Mobile Application for the DD News Channel which is the only terrestrial cum satellite News Channel of the country. The Application Aim to provide the live streaming, News feeds, Top videos . The News Channel of Indias Public Service Broadcaster has been successfully discharging its responsibility to give balanced, fair and accurate news without sensationalizing as well as by carrying different shades of opinion</string>

    <string name="d_desc1">Laxmii is a 2020 Indian Hindi-language horror comedy action film written and directed by Raghava Lawrence, marking his directorial debut in the Hindi film industry. A remake of his own Tamil film Kanchana (2011), it stars Akshay Kumar and Kiara Advani, whilst Ayesha Raza Mishra, Rajesh Sharma, Ashwini Kalsekar and Sharad Kelkar play pivotal roles. The film revolves around a man who gets possessed by the ghost of a transgender person. Kumar, also produced the film under his Cape of Good Films and Fox Star Studios, along with Tusshar Kapoor\'s newly launched production company,[2] Tusshar Entertainment House and Shabinaa Entertainment. Lawrence co-wrote the script along with Farhad Samji, Sparsh Khetarpal, Tasha Bhambra, with Samji adapting the screenplay and dialogues to the Hindi version.[3] The film was announced in January 2019, whilst the principal photography began in April 2019 and ended in March 2020.</string>
    <string name="d_desc2">Criminal Justice is an Indian Hindi-language crime thriller legal drama web series for TV Tips Specials, based on the 2008 British television series of the same name,[1] written by Shridhar Raghavan and was directed by Tigmanshu Dhulia and Vishal Furia. Starring Pankaj Tripathi, Vikrant Massey, Jackie Shroff, Anupriya Goenka and Mita Vashisht in lead roles, the storyline follows life of individuals on a gut wrenching journey through the criminal justice system.</string>
    <string name="d_desc3">Bhoomi (transl. Earth) is an Indian Tamil-language social action drama film, written and directed by Lakshman. This film is produced by Jayam Ravi\'s mother-in-law Sujatha Vijayakumar under the production banner Home Movie Makers.</string>
    <string name="d_desc4">The Falcon and the Winter Soldier[a] is an American television miniseries created by Malcolm Spellman for the streaming service Disney+, featuring the Marvel Comics characters Sam Wilson / Falcon and Bucky Barnes / Winter Soldier. Set in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), it shares continuity with the films of the franchise and takes place after the events of the film Avengers: Endgame (2019). The series was produced by Marvel Studios, with Spellman serving as head writer and Kari Skogland directing.</string>
    <string name="d_desc5">1232 KMS is a 2021 Indian Hindi-language documentary film directed by Vinod Kapri.[1] It chronicles the Indian migrant workers during the COVID-19 pandemic and the impact of the lockdown on them.[2][3] The film was released on Disney+ TV Tips on 24 March 2021</string>
    <string name="d_desc6">OK Computer is an Indian science fiction comedy-drama television series on Disney+ TV Tips created and directed by Pooja Shetty and Neil Pagedar, who also wrote the script along with Anand Gandhi. Gandhi and his team also produced the series through the studio Memesys Culture Lab</string>
    <string name="d_desc7">The Big Bull is a 2021 Indian Hindi-language crime drama film directed and co-written by Kookie Gulati and produced by Ajay Devgn, Anand Pandit, Vikrant Sharma and Kumar Mangat Pathak.</string>
    <string name="d_desc8">City of Dreams is an Indian series by Nagesh Kukunoor which is available on TV Tips on its new label TV Tips Specials from 3 May 2019. It is directed by Nagesh Kukunoor starring Atul Kulkarni, Priya Bapat, Sachin Pilgaonkar, Eijaz Khan and Siddharth Chandekar.</string>
    <string name="d_desc9">Himmat Singh leads a task force searching for the mastermind behind several terrorist attacks.</string>
    <string name="b_desc1">Fast Layne is a live-action Disney Channel miniseries, which ran from February 15, 2019 to March 31. The series follows a brilliant girl named Layne Reed and her friend Zora Morris, who stumble upon an intelligent car named VIN.</string>
    <string name="b_desc2">Little Einsteins is an American interactive animated children\'s television series that aired on Playhouse Disney. ... The series was based on the direct-to-video film of the same name, subtitled Our Huge Adventure.</string>
    <string name="b_desc3">Bizaardvark is an American comedy television series created by Kyle Stegina and Josh Lehrman that aired on Disney Channel from June 24, 2016 to April 13, 2019. The series stars Madison Hu, Olivia Rodrigo, Jake Paul, DeVore Ledridge, Ethan Wacker, Maxwell Simkins, and Elie Samouhi.</string>
    <string name="b_desc4">Austin Moon gains overnight success when he performs one of Ally Dawson\'s songs. But their relationship is ridden with comical situations since both have opposing personalities.</string>
    <string name="b_desc5">Doraemon: A cat-like robot of the 22nd century. Doraemon came to the present age to help Nobita. Doraemon has a four-dimensional pocket which holds a lot of gadgets. He loves Japanese traditional sweet Dorayaki (also called Bean Jam Buns) and suffers from musophobia (fear of mice).</string>
    <string name="b_desc6">It follows the adventures of the five-year-old Shinnosuke Shin Nohara and his parents, baby sister, dog, neighbours, and best friends and is set in Kasukabe, Saitama Prefecture, Japan. Crayon Shin-chan first appeared in 1990 in a Japanese weekly magazine called Weekly Manga Action, which was published by Futabasha.</string>
    <string name="b_desc7">Selfie with Bajrangi is an action-comedy animation TV series set in a small town in contemporary India produced by Cosmos-Maya. ... The series was later acquired by Disney India and was syndicated on Hungama TV and Disney Channel (India). In 2020 Disney India Commissioned 342 episodes for streaming service Disney+TV Tips.</string>
    <string name="b_desc8">The series stars the fearless super-cop Chulbul Pandey and is one of the first animated series to retain the original version of a popular Bollywood character rather than reimagine the star as a kid. Dabangg – The Animated Series is a collaboration of WarnerMedia and Cosmos-Maya, a leading Asian kids\' animation studio.</string>
    <string name="b_desc9">Sofia the First is an American CGI animated children\'s television series that premiered on November 18, 2012, produced by Disney Television Animation for Disney Channel and Disney Junior. Jamie Mitchell is the director and executive producer and Craig Gerber serves as creator, story editor, and producer.</string>
    <string name="h_desc1">Nandini is envied by her stepmother and stepsister who put her through hardships. However, her life takes a turn after she gets married to Darsh, a rich and visually impaired businessman.</string>
    <string name="h_desc2">Saath Nibhaana Saathiya ( transl. Stay together, my love) is an Indian drama television produced by Rashmi Sharma under Rashmi Sharma telefilms. The show premiered on 3 May 2010 on Star Plus. It starred Giaa Manek, Rucha Hasabnis, Mohammad Nazim, Rupal Patel and Devoleena Bhattacharjee.</string>
    <string name="h_desc3">Pandya Store is an Indian television drama series that premiered on 25 January 2021 on StarPlus. The series is a remake of Star Vijay\'s Tamil series Pandian Stores. Produced by Sphere Origins, it stars Shiny Doshi, Kinshuk Mahajan, Kanwar Dhillon, Alice Kaushik, Akshay Kharodia, Simran Budharup and Mohit Parmar.</string>
    <string name="h_desc4">Twins Karthik and Mayan get separated at birth and grow up unaware of each other\'s existence. Their lives change when they marry the woman affianced to the other, who are also stepsisters.</string>
    <string name="h_desc5">Shivaansh, the spoilt son of Shivaay and Annika, becomes a Bollywood actor who goes to any length to achieve success. However, his life takes a turn when he meets Aditi, a no-nonsense police officer.</string>
    <string name="h_desc6">Lord Shiva cannot tolerate injustice and tries to vanquish all the evil forces. Meanwhile, Princess Sati, who is naturally drawn to Lord Shiva, goes to any extent to impress him.</string>
    <string name="h_desc7">Koffee with Karan is an Indian talk show on Star World India hosted by film producer, actor and director Karan Johar. First airing on 19 November 2004, it is the second longest-running talk show after Phool Khile Hain Gulshan Gulshan in Indian television. The show concluded its sixth season on 17 March 2019.</string>
    <string name="h_desc8">Anupamaa is an Indian drama television series that premiered on 13 July 2020 on Star Plus. Produced by Rajan Shahi and Deepa Shahi under Director\'s Kut Productions, it stars Rupali Ganguly in the titular role. It is based on Star Jalsha\'s Bengali series Sreemoyee.</string>
    <string name="a_desc1">Mira, Royal Detective is an American-Indian CGI-animated mystery children\'s television series produced by Wild Canary Animation, which is inspired by Indian culture and customs. The show\'s protagonist, Mira, is the first South Asian protagonist in a Disney Junior show.</string>
    <string name="a_desc2">Mickey Mouse is a cartoon character created in 1928 by The Walt Disney Company, who also serves as the brand\'s mascot. An anthropomorphic mouse who typically wears red shorts, large yellow shoes, and white gloves, Mickey is one of the world\'s most recognizable fictional characters.</string>
    <string name="a_desc3">Oye Golu is a Disney Channel India animated series that premiered on May 5th, 2019. It is about a boy named Adi and his best friend, a genie named Golu, who often uses his magic to help him solve everyday problems. ... In 2020, the series was made available on the Indian version of Disney+.</string>
    <string name="a_desc4">Mickey Mouse is a cartoon character created in 1928 by The Walt Disney Company, who also serves as the brand\'s mascot. An anthropomorphic mouse who typically wears red shorts, large yellow shoes, and white gloves, Mickey is one of the world\'s most recognizable fictional characters.</string>
    <string name="a_desc5">Selfie with Bajrangi is an action-comedy animation TV series set in a small town in contemporary India produced by Cosmos-Maya. ... The series was later acquired by Disney India and was syndicated on Hungama TV and Disney Channel (India). In 2020 Disney India Commissioned 342 episodes for streaming service Disney+TV Tips.</string>
    <string name="a_desc6">Little Einsteins is an American interactive animated children\'s television series that aired on Playhouse Disney. ... The series was based on the direct-to-video film of the same name, subtitled Our Huge Adventure.</string>
    <string name="a_desc7">TaleSpin is an American animated television series first aired in 1990 as a preview on Disney Channel and later that year as part of The Disney Afternoon. ... Namely Baloo the Bear, Louie the ape, and Shere Khan the tiger, along with new characters created for the show.</string>
    <string name="a_desc8">Recess portrays the lives of six fourth graders—cheeky and popular lovable rogue Theodore Jasper T.J. Detweiler (Ross Malinger, Andrew Lawrence), Jock Vince LaSalle (Rickey D\'Shon Collins), tomboy Ashley Spinelli (Pamela Adlon), wise fool Mikey Blumberg (Jason Davis), geek Gretchen Grundler (Ashley Johnson)</string>
    <string name="a_desc9">Quack Pack is an American animated sitcom produced by Walt Disney Television Animation, featuring Donald Duck and his nephews. The show debuted on September 3, 1996 as a part of the Disney Afternoon programming block, following the success of Goof Troop. The series ran for one season with 39 episodes.</string>
    <string name="g_desc1">Three brothers are set to marry three sisters. However, a peek into the distant past reveals to one of the brothers that their brides have been mixed up in their current reincarnation.</string>
    <string name="g_desc2">After Thanos, an intergalactic warlord, disintegrates half of the universe, the Avengers must reunite and assemble again to reinvigorate their trounced allies and restore balance.</string>
    <string name="g_desc3">The Avengers must stop Thanos, an intergalactic warlord, from getting his hands on all the infinity stones. However, Thanos is prepared to go to any lengths to carry out his insane plan.</string>
    <string name="g_desc4">Nick Fury is compelled to launch the Avengers Initiative when Loki poses a threat to planet Earth. His squad of superheroes put their minds together to accomplish the task.</string>
    <string name="g_desc5">Though Champak initially disapproves, he eventually does everything in his power while going through a series of hilarious mishaps to fulfil his daughter\'s dream of going to London to study further.</string>
    <string name="g_desc6">An elite team of the Indian intelligence system perpetually strives to detect and eliminate terrorists and their plots. Officer Ajay leads a team to destroy one such potentially lethal operation.</string>
    <string name="g_desc7">Aftermath is a 2017 American drama thriller film directed by Elliott Lester and written by Javier Gullón. ... The film is based on events and persons surrounding the 2002 Überlingen mid-air collision of a passenger airliner with a cargo jet, although the names, places, nationalities, and incidents were changed.</string>
    <string name="g_desc8">A girl who has her first period and do not get any respect from the society.</string>
    <string name="g_desc9">Super 30 is a 2019 Indian Hindi-language biographical drama film directed by Vikas Bahl and produced by Phantom Films, Reliance Entertainment, Nadiadwala Grandson Entertainment &amp; HRX Films, The story revolves around mathematics teacher and educator Anand Kumar and his educational program of the same name.</string>
    <string name="f_desc1">Tanhaji: The Unsung Warrior is a 2020 Indian Hindi-language period action film co-written and directed by Om Raut and produced by Bhushan Kumar, Krishan Kumar and Ajay Devgn under T-Series Films and Ajay Devgn FFilms. ... The film was launched on 20 July 2017, with Raut making his directorial debut in Bollywood.</string>
    <string name="f_desc2">Ronnie, a young man, shares a deep bond with Vikram, his elder brother and a policeman. When Vikram gets kidnapped in Syria while on a mission, Ronnie sets out to rescue him.</string>
    <string name="f_desc3">Set in the Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU), it shares continuity with the films of the franchise and takes place after the events of the film Avengers: Endgame (2019). ... The Falcon and the Winter Soldier premiered on March 19, 2021, and ran for six episodes until April 23. It is part of Phase Four of the MCU.</string>
    <string name="f_desc4">Kabir and Junaid, two policemen at odds with each other, embark on a mission to the Middle East to rescue Viraj, a leading cricketer who has been kidnapped.</string>
    <string name="f_desc5">Since “Taqdeer” is the story of a music teacher\'s fight with fate, it had to feature quality and engaging singers. ... He teaches his children, Geeta (Farida Jalal), Mala (Kajal) and Sushil (Sushil Kumar), a song that later helps him recover his memory in far away Africa when one of his students sings at a function</string>
    <string name="f_desc6">Shaolin (also known as The New Shaolin Temple) is a 2011 Hong Kong martial arts film produced and directed by Benny Chan, starring Andy Lau and Nicholas Tse, with a special appearance by Jackie Chan. ... The film was also released in Mandarin and Cantonese languages.</string>
    <string name="f_desc7">India\'s Most Wanted is a 2019 Indian Hindi-language action thriller film directed by Raj Kumar Gupta, and starring Arjun Kapoor. The film is about tracking a terrorist in a secret mission and arresting him without firing bullets.</string>
    <string name="f_desc8">An elite team of the Indian intelligence system perpetually strives to detect and eliminate terrorists and their plots. Officer Ajay leads a team to destroy one such potentially lethal operation.</string>
    <string name="f_desc9">Avengers: Infinity War is a 2018 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team the Avengers. ... In the film, the Avengers and the Guardians of the Galaxy attempt to prevent Thanos from collecting the six all-powerful Infinity Stones as part of his quest to kill half of all life in the universe.</string>
    <string name="latesttrend">Latest &amp; Treading</string>
    <string name="seemore">More</string>
    <string name="poptv">Popular TV Show</string>
    <string name="popular">Popular Movies</string>
    <string name="popaction">Popular In Action</string>
    <string name="bestofkids">Best For Kids</string>
    <string name="bestfriend">Best Friends Forever</string>

    <string name="retry">Retry Again</string>
    <string name="connect_internet">Please Connect To Internet</string>
    <string name="notify">notification</string>

</resources>